stuffandnonsense.co.uk 2007-12-17

# Privacy policy | Stuff and Nonsense

## Privacy policy

We respect your privacy as we hate receiving offers of money from mysteriously generous Nigerians as much as you do. If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy in relation to our site, please [contact](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/company/contact) Andy Clarke or telephone [+44 1745 851848](callto:44-1745-851848).

#### Information collection and use

We collect personal information when you complete forms such as newsletter registrations and contact forms. We are the sole owner of the information collected about you on this site and we do not sell, share, or rent this information to anyone else. We always treat your information fairly and in full compliance to the Data Protection Act 1988.

#### Cookies

Our web site does not use persistent cookies. We do use cookies which last for the duration of your visit. These cookies allow us to provide you with an enhanced visiting experience. They do not contain any personal information and once you close your web browser it deletes these cookies.

#### Log files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information to help us understand what browsers and operating systems our visitors use. They also tell us the most popular pages on our site and how our visitors found our site on a search engine. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information, so we can't tell where you live, where your children go to school, or what colour is your underwear (black).

#### Links

Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects any personally identifiable information. So please stay aware, wear wellington boots and practise safe browsing.

### About Stuff and Nonsense

Stuff and Nonsense is a small, but popular web design studio, founded and led by designer and author [Andy Clarke](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/company/about#andy). We started back in 1998 and have built a enviable reputation for creating highly effective web sites, ecommerce stores and web applications for our clients.

### Want to work with us?

[Send us an email](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/company/contact) or fill in our project sheet and well send you an outline quote within one week.

Download our request for quotation sheet in [Word format (60kb)](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/downloads/rfq_2007.doc "download in Word format") or [PDF format (150kb)](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/downloads/rfq_2007.pdf "download in PDF format").
